**Effective Date: March 1, 2023**
---------------------------------

Please note that Nelnet Campus Commerce (“Campus Commerce”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) offers Services related to education, including tuition management, payment administration and processing, financial needs assessment, school management, online application, and online enrollment. To provide these Services, we must store and maintain information about educational institutions (or other entities) we serve, along with personal information regarding administrators, staff members, parents, and students. Access to the data will be restricted to authorized associates and will be used only for the purpose of providing Services to you or the Institution.

**Online Privacy Policy**
-------------------------

Nelnet or one of its affiliates operates this mobile device application or this Website. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) is designed to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of products and services (individually and collectively, the “Services”) through the Website, as well as from users of Nelnet’s mobile device application(s). This Policy applies to users who are located in the U.S. when visiting the Website.

We are committed to providing you a useful and enjoyable online experience. This Policy explains our collection and use practices regarding consumer information, including how and what we share with our related companies and with unrelated entities. Protecting your privacy is important to Nelnet and our employees. We want you to understand what information we collect and how we use it.

This Policy is subject to change from time to time, so be sure to check back occasionally to ensure you have read the most current version. It is effective as of the date listed above and applies to our Services that link to this policy. Even if you read and/or agreed to a prior privacy statement, you need to review this updated version. We reserve the right at any time, and in our sole discretion, to change or modify this Policy. If any such changes or modifications are made, we will update the “Effective Date” appearing at the top of this web page. Such changes or modifications shall be effective immediately upon posting to the Website, and supersede any prior versions of this Policy.

This Policy governs the privacy policies of this Website or the Nelnet Campus Commerce mobile device application(s) only.

**Information we collect**
--------------------------

### Why We Collect Information

We collect information so we can identify you as our customer, to establish, manage and protect your accounts, to complete your transactions, to create and offer you products and services you might be interested in, to personalize and improve upon your experience with us and to comply with various legal and regulatory requirements.

### Non-Identifying Information

We may collect information from your visit or as part of the registration and administration of your account, in order to personalize and improve upon your experience with us, such as, without limitation, age and individual preferences (“Non-Identifying Information”).

### Cookies

The Services may place “Cookies” on a visitor’s device. Cookies are small text files. Our Cookies save anonymized data about individual visitors, allowing our Services to recognize information about a visitor and help deliver personalized content and other services and functions. Cookies make your Internet experience quicker and more convenient. The Services use both session cookies, which terminate when a user closes his or her browser, and persistent cookies, which remain on the user’s device until they expire or are manually deleted. The Services also contain coding from our business and technology partners which generates third party cookies. Third party cookies allow our business and technology partners to store non-Identifying Information they can access when you visit this or other websites. Accepting a cookie from a web or device browser may give us access to Personally Identifiable Information for analytics purposes.

Most website and mobile device browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and provide the ability to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Blocking cookies may result in a lower quality experience for you while you are using our Services.

### Device and Connection Information

When you use our Services, we will identify the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer or handheld device. The IP address does not identify you personally, but it lets us identify the device you are using. We store IP addresses in case we need to track a connection for security purposes. We may also collect other device-specific information about the device you are using, including what type of device it is and hardware model, what operating system you are using, device settings, unique device identified, geo-location data, and crash data. Whether we collect some or all of this information often depends on what type of device you are using and its settings. Check the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider to learn more about what information your device makes available to us.

### Web Beacons (1×1 Pixels or GIFS)

Our Services may contain coding known as Web Beacons that use 1×1 pixel images to capture and transmit the online activity of users on our Services. These Web Beacons typically transmit information about form completions and other activities in order to measure advertising effectiveness or store analytics information. In addition, we may use Web Beacons in HTML-based emails. This allows us to evaluate the effectiveness of our email communications and our marketing campaigns by showing how many emails recipients have opened.

### Log Files

Like most websites, our servers utilize log files. Log files store information including internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. Log files are used to analyze trends, administer the Website, track Users’ movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We use log file information at times to help identify you as you browse and to gather broad technical and demographic information on who uses our website.

### Google Analytics Feature

We may use Google Analytics to collect information about the use of the Website. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit the Website, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to the Website. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve the Website. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit the Website, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with Personally Identifiable Information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this Website by [disabling the Google Analytics cookie on your browser](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). You can also view and change the [currently available opt-outs](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en) for Google Ads.

### Other Analytics Tools

In addition to or in lieu of Google Analytics, we may use other similar web analytics tools to collect information about our Website. Regardless of the tool selected, we use this information only to improve the Website. Any analytics tools we use collect the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit the Website, your name and email address. We only use analytics tools that are GDPR-compliant and that meet our auditing and privacy standards.

### Google Drive

If you choose to link your Google Drive account to a Nelnet Campus Commerce product for easy access to your files, Nelnet Campus Commerce will use Google’s OAuth protocols to establish that connection. Nelnet Campus Commerce will not use this information in any manner inconsistent with this policy or for any purpose other than allowing you access to your Google Drive. Nelnet Campus Commerce will not read, edit, delete, or copy files or information without your permission or as instructed by you. You may disconnect Nelnet Campus Commerce’s site or application at any time by removing access through your Google account.

### Do Not Track Signals

Do Not Track is a feature in your web browser, which enables you to opt-out of the third party tracking of your online activities over time and across third party websites. We do not track users across third party websites to provide targeted advertising, and therefore, do not process or comply with any web browser’s “do not track” signal or other similar mechanism that indicates a request to disable online tracking of individual users who visit this Website or use our Services. Third parties cannot collect any Personally Identifiable Information from this Website unless you provide it to them directly.

### Personally Identifying Information

We may collect Nonpublic Personal Information about you from the following sources:

* Information from this Website or paper forms
* Information about your transactions with us or others
* Information we receive from third parties, such as your academic institution

“Nonpublic Personal Information” is nonpublic, personally identifiable financial information about you that we obtain in connection with providing a financial product or service to you. For example, Nonpublic Personal Information includes information regarding your account balance, payment history, and overdraft history, if applicable.

We may collect Personally Identifiable Information about you as well, including:

* Your first and last name
* Your home address
* Your home or work telephone number
* Your birth date
* Your email address
* Credit Card Number
* Bank Account Number
* Bank Routing Number
* Username and Password
* Student ID

“Personally Identifiable Information” is individually identifiable information about an individual consumer collected by us and maintained in an accessible form.

**How We Use Your Information**
-------------------------------

### Uses of Information

Certain Non-Identifying Information would be considered a part of your Personally Identifiable Information if it were combined with other identifiers (for example, combining your zip code with your street address) in a way that enables you to be identified. But the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other non-identifying information (for example, your viewing preferences). We may combine your Personally Identifiable Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other Users to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Services and to analyze and understand how our Website and Services are used. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically, for instance to deliver a product to you according to your preferences or restrictions.

If you supply us with your e-mail address, we may let you know by e-mail about other products and services and product enhancements that may be of interest to you. You will have the opportunity to tell us you do not want to receive future messages with each message you receive. If you e-mail a question or comment to us, we will use your e-mail address to reply to you and we will temporarily store your e-mail address, your message, and our reply for quality assurance or to satisfy applicable laws and regulations. When we collect your e-mail address this way, we will not use it for marketing our products and services unless you have given us permission.

If you wish to change any of your personal information, you may change it by logging into your account; by contacting Customer Service, either through email, mail, or telephone; or by contacting your Educational Institution.

### What We Share

We do not sell personal information to third parties. All personal information collected is used by us or our affiliates to perform services, comply with laws or carry out internal functions.

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Services, to provide the Services on our behalf, to perform Website-related Services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Website’s features) to assist us in analyzing how our Website and Services are used, or to perform other services (e.g., without limitation, sending postal mail and email, providing marketing assistance, and providing customer service). These third parties have access to your Nonpublic Personal Information, Nonpublic Personal Information, and/or Personally Identifiable Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf; provided, however, that if you are redirected to a site or application maintained by a third party, the privacy policy of such site or application will control the use of any information you provide.

We may share your information with companies that are affiliated with us, such as our direct or indirect subsidiaries or parent or sister companies. As we continue to develop our business, we may buy or sell companies, subsidiaries, or business units. Your Personally Identifiable Information may be included as an asset in connection with mergers, acquisitions, reorganizations, or sales of assets including in the event of bankruptcy.

Sometimes the law or other circumstances also require that we disclose Nonpublic Personal Information and/or Personally Identifiable Information about you to nonaffiliated third parties. Some examples are: when you ask or permit us to do so; in response to subpoenas or court orders; when we suspect fraud or criminal activity; to protect our property and rights or those of a third party; to protect the safety of the public or any person; or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity.

VERMONT RESIDENTS: We will not disclose nonpublic personal financial information about you other than as permitted by law unless you authorize us to make that disclosure. Your authorization must be in writing or, if you agree, in electronic form. If you wish to authorize us to disclose your nonpublic personal financial information to nonaffiliated third parties, you may notify us at the address found under the “How to Contact Us” section below.

If you become an inactive User, we will continue to adhere to the privacy policies and practices described in this Policy.

### Our Security Procedures

We are committed to providing you a useful and enjoyable online experience. We implement reasonable and appropriate physical, procedural, and electronic safeguards to protect your information.

To access information and send e-mail via the Website, you will need a browser that supports the use of Transport Layer Security protocols. This encryption technology helps ensure the authenticity of your online sessions and secures data being transmitted over the public Internet.

We take careful steps to safeguard customer information. We restrict access to your personal and account information to those employees who need to know that information to provide Services to you, and we regularly train our employees on privacy, information security, and their obligation to protect your information. We maintain reasonable and appropriate physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard your Nonpublic Personal Information and Personally Identifiable Information and we regularly test those safeguards to maintain the appropriate levels of protection.

You can help safeguard your Nonpublic Personal Information and Personally Identifiable Information by taking a few simple precautions. Protect your account numbers, passwords, and customer access numbers. Never disclose confidential information to unknown callers. You should always use a secure browser and current virus detection software, and never open email from unknown sources.

### Children’s Privacy

The Website is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use personally identifiable information from children under age 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us Personally Identifiable Information without their consent, he or she should contact us using the information in the “How to Contact Us” section, below. If we confirm we have collected such information, we will take all reasonable measures to delete that information from our system as soon as possible. For users of our learning management system and related products, we may collect and store certain information as required to provide learning management tools to schools, teachers, and students who use such tools.

### Links to Other Websites and Services

We are not responsible for the collection and use of information by companies or individuals unaffiliated with us whose websites may contain links to the Website, including vendors where you may shop. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Website to another website, our Policy does not apply to third party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third party website or service are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies. Please note that when you shop with a vendor who is linked to the Website, even though you may have started your visit with us, and even though our pages may still appear, your transactions are completed with a separate organization, not with us. In addition, you agree that we are not responsible and we do not have control over any third parties that you authorize to access your user content. If you are using a third party website or service, and you allow such a third party access to your user content, you do so at your own risk. This Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources other than through the Website and applications.

### California Resident Disclosure

The California Consumer Protection Act provides California Residents with specific rights regarding their personal information. This section describes how we treat your personal information in light of the CCPA. As stated above, we do not disclose nonpublic personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties. We do not sell your personal information, and only use your personal information for the following reasons:

* Provide consumer services.
* Comply with the law.
* Carry out the internal functions.

_Right of Access, Correction, and Deletion_

Consumers have the right to access, correct, and have their information deleted if the information is no longer needed to provide the services they’ve requested. To submit a request to exercise any of these rights please email [**AskPrivacy@nelnet.net**.](mailto:AskPrivacy@nelnet.net)

**How to Contact Us**
---------------------

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us by email or regular mail at the following address:

Nelnet Campus Commerce  
121 South 13th Street, Suite 301  
Lincoln, NE 68508  
Email: [AskPrivacy@nelnet.net](mailto:AskPrivacy@nelnet.net)

**Effective Date: May 25, 2018**

How We Use Your Information
---------------------------

### Categories of Information

By providing our services, we may from time to time collect, store, use or process your personal information for legitimate business purposes, such as improving our products and services. Nelnet Campus Commerce collects the following categories of personal information:

* Your first and last name
* Your home address
* Your home or work telephone number
* Your birth date
* Your email address

“Personal information” is defined as information related to identified or identifiable natural persons recorded by electronic or other means, excluding the information processed anonymously.

“Sensitive Personal Information” is defined as personal information that, once leaked, or illegally used, may easily infringe the dignity of a natural person or cause harm to personal safety and property security, such as biometric identification information, religious beliefs, specifically-designated status, medical health information, financial accounts, information on individuals’ whereabouts, as well as personal information of minors under the age of 14.

### Uses of Information

With your consent, we may use your personal information and aggregate it with information collected from other users to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the services and to analyze and understand how our website and services are used. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically, for instance to deliver a product to you according to your preferences or restrictions.

If you supply us with your e-mail address, we may let you know by e-mail about other products and services and product enhancements that may be of interest to you. You will have the opportunity to tell us you do not want to receive future messages with each message you receive. If you e-mail a question or comment to us, we will use your e-mail address to reply to you and we will temporarily store your e-mail address, your message, and our reply for quality assurance or to satisfy applicable laws and regulations. When we collect your e-mail address this way, we will not use it for marketing our products and services unless you have given us permission.

Nelnet Campus Commerce will only use your personal information for the purpose for which it was collected and will only use the information when necessary in accordance with that purpose. Nelnet Campus Commerce will only use your personal information on the following legal bases:

* With your consent.
* Where it is necessary to conclude or perform a contract.
* Where it is necessary to perform statutory responsibilities or statutory obligations.

If Nelnet Campus Commerce is required to process your Sensitive Personal Information, Nelnet Campus Commerce will request your separate consent unless another legal basis for processing exists.

### What We Share

We do not sell personal information to third parties. All personal information collected is used by us or our affiliates to perform services, comply with laws or carry out internal functions.

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Services, to provide the Services on our behalf, to perform Website-related Services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Website’s features) to assist us in analyzing how our Website and Services are used, or to perform other services (e.g., without limitation, sending postal mail and email, providing marketing assistance, and providing customer service). These third parties have access to your personal information only to perform these tasks on our behalf; provided, however, that if you are redirected to a site or application maintained by a third party, the privacy policy of such site or application will control the use of any information you provide.

We may share your information with companies that are affiliated with us, such as our direct or indirect subsidiaries or parent or sister companies. As we continue to develop our business, we may buy or sell companies, subsidiaries, or business units. Your Personal Information may be included as an asset in connection with mergers, acquisitions, reorganizations, or sales of assets including in the event of bankruptcy.

Sometimes the law or other circumstances also require that we disclose Personal Information about you to nonaffiliated third parties. Some examples are: when you ask or permit us to do so; in response to subpoenas or court orders; when we suspect fraud or criminal activity; to protect our property and rights or those of a third party; to protect the safety of the public or any person; or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity.

### How to Exercise Your Rights

To exercise your rights with Nelnet Campus Commerce, except the right to file a lawsuit in a court of competent jurisdiction, you may submit your request to the following to Customer Service, either through email, mail, or telephone; or by contacting your Educational Institution. You may request access to or deletion of your information by contacting [AskPrivacy@nelnet.net](mailto:AskPrivacy@nelnet.net).

Customer Service:  
Nelnet Campus Commerce  
121 South 13th Street, Suite 301  
Lincoln, NE 68508  

You will be asked to identify yourself and authenticate your identity, what information you are concerned about, and what right(s) you are exercising.

Nelnet Campus Commerce will respond to your request in accordance with applicable laws and regulations and existing policies and procedures.

### Information Transfers

Although your data is generally stored within the United States, an international data transfer may occur if third party, cloud-based storage companies that Nelnet Campus Commerce employs use servers located outside the United States. Nelnet Campus Commerce uses appropriate technical and organizational security measures including encryption of personal data and follows various industry standards and best practices to protect your personal data. Additionally, Nelnet Campus Commerce requires its vendors and processors to abide by PIPL and to apply adequate security and technical safeguards.

**Contact Details for Privacy and Data-related Inquiries**
----------------------------------------------------------

**Data Controller:**

Contact Your Educational Institution or Merchant

**Data Processor:**  
Chief Compliance Officer
